(Sheldon:)I was too busy
trying not to defecate.
(Leonard:)You know, when they were
escorting us
(Leonard:)to the detaining room,
I looked through a door,
(Leonard:)and I'm pretty sure
I saw a display case
(Leonard:)with the Ark
of the Covenant.
(Sheldon:)That's amazing.
(chuckling):
I know.
(Sheldon:)And I saw Jabba the Hutt
riding by on a motorcycle.
(Sheldon:)Although that was
right after the Tasing,
(Sheldon:)so who can
say for sure?
I-I guess this could count
as an adventure.
(Howard:)It was.
(Sheldon:)And even though we're
not allowed back there,
(Sheldon:)they can never take
today away from us.
(Sheldon:)Unlike my sense
of smell,
(Sheldon:)which hasn't returned
since the Tasing.
(sniffs)
(Sheldon:)No, I got nothing.
(panting): Amy, the Daleks
are right on my tail!
(Sheldon:)Quick, we need to reset
the time circuits.
(Sheldon:)Oh, no, I left my sonic
screwdriver behind.
(Amy:)Really should have
thought this through.